Amoresi launched a sub-brand and a few weeks ago I ordered a bunch of tights and catsuits
because Amoti, the sub-brand, specializes on nylons and pantyhoses.
So I will try a few things on and show it to you.
I always say I don't collect anything but I have two huge boxes of tights so I hoard tights
and these will go into them as well.
The good thing is my Amoresi discount code works for Amoti too so you can get a discount and they have a mail section so tight for me. I have to check out what I ordered again and it comes in these cute cute cute little boxes which will look nice on the shelf and are great to store the products in.
And they make great gifts too because you can simply hand over a present in the box itself. These are some gloves, nylon gloves. I have them in blue and in nude and these are the black ones.
Let's see if I can get into them.
I'm just confused, don't mind me.
Oh, these are actually pretty nice. They feel really soft and really comfy.
They're not too thick.
And I love the shine.
Nice.
This one feels a bit rougher and it looks almost a bit bluish when I am not wearing
it but now it looks more black.
It still has a blue tint to it now when I'm sitting I can see it better and it almost
looks like it has a very closely knit fishnet structure and it also has an open crush area
which is kind of handy.
at this it's so tiny did I order the wrong size or can I fit into it okay
let's try this it took me a little while but I got into it it's really very tight
but on the other hand it's really stretchy so it does work and I got into
it and it's really long which is really cool because I feel so comfortable not
being too short and not feeling like you have to stretch the garment too much but
it's really long I have a lot of leftover fabric basically and yeah the
gloves fit the arms fit the legs fit it's really really cool I love it and I
also love the shine I try to move the lights a bit more towards me so you can
see to shine better. I hope it works. It has a back zipper which is really handy. I figure
you could like use it as a neck entry as well because it's so stretchy. Like I can do this
and it doesn't rip. Really cool. Love it. In Germany we would say Körperkondom which
translated to body condom full body condom because it fits so snug it's
really really soft it almost feels a bit slippery in my hands trying to not poke
holes in the tights with my nails I got them done for the first time and I'm
trying to not look too ungraceful now
This is an interesting color, like a kind of nude.
And yes, I'm doing pull dance, so excuse all the bruises, but that's not uncommon.
I love the color it matches really well with my rather pale skin and it's really
comfy I did not just try them so far which is a great sign me not destroying
tights when I first wear them is always good and I can't really remember all the
names but I will put them down in the description text of the video so check
that one out you know me by now if I see something blue I have to try it and in
this case I did not only find tights in blue but also the matching gloves and I
I hope it's going to look good together.
These are longer than just elbow length.
But again, really smooth and also the tights super soft and really shiny for tights.
I don't know if you can see it in the light. I will try to capture it.
I think it's a nice combination.
And I'm wearing a dress which has an open back, so of course not the ideal option.
but I wanted to show this combination with a little black dress.
I hope that it's the same color and I think if you ignore my hat
I look a bit like a Smurf. And we
on to the next one.
As a true goth I do love a good fishnet tights.
Because you can
always match anything with fishnets at least in my opinion
I have like a really white
net, netted fishnet
netted fishnet at the moment but there are also
some with a smaller net and even white ones
I'm really curious about that one
because it's a thick tight
and it has some footholds so no socks
okay this almost looks like a see-through tights like a really thin one
but it's in fact really thick it's just a look-alike of the thin tights it's really
comfy it's really warm it's definitely something for winter what I love about this is that I can
actually wear my socks and my thick socks in my shoes to not get cold feet but the tights
still stay in place because they're anchored to my feet here that was it for today I hope you
enjoyed this little trip into the world of pantyhoses and nylons and if you did
check out the Amoti shop I'll link it down below don't forget my discount code
which works for Amoti but also for Amoresi they make a lot of spandex
clothes I have a few videos up here on my channel so check them out and I still
love these boxes so cool anyway hope to see you in the next video again leave a
thumbs up here and write a comment below the video have a nice day bye